# Do Le Long An

dolelongan@gmail.com | 0937022184 | SkyGarden 3, Phu My Hung Residential Area, District 7

## ABOUT ME

Having previously majored in Computer Science and Data Science at UWA, I am now studying at RMIT University in Vietnam, majoring in Information Technology. Due to my experience leading most of my projects, I developed the soft skills of Time Management and Leadership.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Foundation Program - Advanced**

Taylor's College Graduated with *GPA* 3.0/4.0 10/2019 - 06/2020

## **B.Sc. in Computer Science and Data Science**

University of Western Australia 07/2020 - 12/2021

#### **B.IT. in Web Development**

RMIT University Vietnam *GPA 3.4/4.0* 06/2022 - Current

## **LINKS**

LaansDole

in do-le-long-an

laansdole

## **HONORS & AWARDS**

10/2019 - Taylors College Foundation Program Highest Scholarship -7,500AUD.

06/2020 - Australia's Global Excellence Scholarship - 15,000AUD per anum.

2021 - Best Regional Marketing Member in AIESEC Australia 2021.2.

## VOLUNTEER

12/2019 - 03/2020 - StudyPerth Airport Greeter

 Guide and assist foreign students and guests at Perth Airport, Western Australia

## PROJECT EXPERIENCE

#### **RBLOG** - Front End Developer

RMIT Vietnam - Building IT System - COSC2634

- Tech Stack used: MEN (MongoDB + Express + React + Node.js)
- · CSS Framework: Tailwind
- Objective: Giving the blogging community a platform that is easy to use.
- · Link to Website Demo: rmit-blog

#### E-Commerce Website - Project Leader

04/2023 - 05/2023

10/2022 - 01/2023

RMIT Vietnam - Web Programming - COSC2430

- Tech Stack used: MEN (MongoDB + Express + EJS + Node.js)
- CSS Framework: Bootstrap
- Objective: Our intention is to create an e-commerce website that draws inspiration from Lazada but simplifies the user interface and functionality.
- Link to Web App Demo: group9-eCommerce
- Link to Project GitHub repository: group9-eCommerce

#### Resume Builder

31/05/2023

- · Language used: LaTeX
- · Objective: Creating my own resume
- · Link to GitHub repository

## SKILLS

#### **AWS Academy Graduate - AWS Academy Cloud Foundations**

03/2023 - 30/05/2023

RMIT Vietnam - Cloud Foundation - COSC2766

- Completion of AWS Cloud Practitioner Preparation.
- · Link to Cloud Foundation Badge

#### **Data Structure and Algorithm**

03/2023 - 30/05/2023

RMIT Vietnam - Data Structure and Algorithm - COSC2658

- · Language used: Java
- Problem-solving paradigms such as divide and conquer, decrease and conquer, greedy, and dynamic programming.
- · Link to Group Project repository

## Others

06/2022 - Current

RMIT Vietnam - Software Engineering Design - EEET2482

• C++ Group Project

## **CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

#### Micro:bit Automatic Plant Watering

07/2022 - 09/2022

RMIT Vietnam - NCT Club

Participating in developing Micro:bit Automatic Plant Watering

## **NCT Landing Page**

11/2022 - 03/2023

RMIT Vietnam - NCT Club

• Participating in developing NCT Landing page

#### **RMIT Business Plan Competition**

05/2023 - Current

RMIT Vietnam - FinTec Club

• Participating in developing Event Landing Page

Last updated May 31, 2023